question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The word 'news' originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass "
                    "(North, East, West, South).",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "'Santa Claus' is a variety of melon.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "'Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.' "
                    "is a grammatically correct sentence.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The French word to travel is 'Travail'",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food "
                    "to include a source of Vitamin C.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    }
]
